citibank.com.ph 2013-05-29

# Citibank Philippines

|   
---  
|  |  |   
---  
|   
---  
Privacy for Consumers at Citi  
  
Our goal is to maintain your trust and confidence when handling personal information about you.   
  
You Have Choices  
  
As a Citi customer, you have the opportunity to make choices about how personal information about you may be shared. As you consider this, we encourage you to make choices that enable us to provide you with quality products and services that help you meet your financial needs and objectives.   
  
Security of Personal Information:  
| The security of personal information about you is our priority. We protect this information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet applicable law. We train our employees in the proper handling of personal information. When we use other companies to provide services for us, we require them to protect the confidentiality of personal information they receive.   
---  
**Citibank's Internet Privacy Policy**  
This section explains our policy regarding any personal information you might supply to us when you visit this site. Our goal is to protect your information on the Internet in the same way that we protect it in all the other ways we interact with you: in branches, at ATMs, and on the phone.   
  
  * You can visit this site and find out about our products and services or use other value-added services without giving us any information about yourself.
  * There are instances where certain types of information may be requested from our customers via Citibank's website. These may occur when there is an online application for a specific banking product or for authentication into secure areas of the website. If you do provide personal information, please refer to the "Privacy for Consumers at Citi".

**Use of Cookies**  
In order to provide better service or to address security hazards, we will occasionally use a "cookie". A cookie is a small piece of information which a Web site stores on your Web browser on your PC and can later retrieve. The cookie cannot be read by a Web site other than the one that set the cookie. We use cookies for a number of administrative purposes; for example, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information. Most cookies last only through a single session, or visit to our site. None will contain information that will enable anyone to contact you via telephone, e-mail, or any other means. You can set up your Web browser to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set. However, if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to use some of our online services or website features.   
Your browser software may contain a feature which is intended to notify you of the cookie policies of the various web sites you visit. For example, the Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 browser software contained in Microsoft Windows XP contains a version of such a cookie-filtering device, commonly known as P3P. To learn more about P3P and how it may affect your online experience go to www.w3.org/P3P. Citibank has attempted to make our website compatible with the P3P privacy filtering tool. However, P3P is still an evolving standard and therefore, we are not responsible for any problems you may experience when using a P3P filter, or any discrepancies between the machine-coded statements of our privacy policy which are read by the P3P tool and the human readable policy which you see here and in the Privacy for Consumers at Citi. This Internet Privacy Policy and the Privacy for Consumers at Citi are the controlling documents to which you should refer if you have questions about Citibank's privacy policies. The human readable privacy policy is the only binding legal statement and prevails over any discrepancies from the machine readable privacy policy.   
For more details, please check our business sites.   
This page was last updated on July 18, 2008.  
We may change this statement from time to time, so please check periodically.   
Copyright © 2007 Citigroup Inc.
